Guide to the Richard H. Lawrence Photographs, circa 1885-1889 PR 032
New-York Historical Society
- Photographic prints
  - 184. Skating in Central Park, the Nevada Flats in distance, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - 185. N.Y. Central train, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - 186. [(Catholic) church at cobbled street corner; two women], undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - 187. [Group of men with large canisters (fireworks), surrounded by group of policemen; in dark (underground) room], undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Item not stamped with "Photograph by Richard-Hoe-Lawrence / Gift of Mrs. Richard Hoe Lawrence, 1950" as are others; the provenance is thus subject to some question.
  - 188. [Interior view of general store], undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - 189. [Interior view of tobacconist's shop], undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - 190. Washington Inaugural—Naval Parade, [1889?] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
    Separated Materials
    Item was removed December 27, 1988.